=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 3=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 3 =
Is this the file
هل هذا هو الملف
you are looking for?
أنت تبحث عن؟
(I'm the biggest fool in the world.)
(أنا أكبر أحمق في العالم).
I just want to see
انا فقط اريد ان ارى
if someone
اذا كان شخص ما
is really
هو حقا
the biggest fool
أكبر أحمق
in the world.
في العالم.
What?
ماذا؟
It hurts?
هذا مؤلم؟
But I remember
لكني أتذكر
you can't feel your legs.
لا يمكنك الشعور بساقيك.
No,
رقم،
I must be hallucinating.
لا بد أني أكون مهلوسًا.
I am hallucinating.
أنا أهذي.
So you pretended to be lame
لذلك تظاهرت بأنك أعرج
to make my...
لأجعل ...
me
أنا
call off the engagement.
إلغاء المشاركة.
No.
رقم.
It's because of my brother Mo Feng.
إنه بسبب أخي مو فنغ.
Your brother?
أخوك؟
My half-brother.
أخي غير الشقيق.
He's been forced by his mother
لقد أجبرته والدته
to surpass me since he was a kid.
ليتفوق عليّ منذ أن كان طفلاً.
Something is wrong with him here.
هناك شيء خاطئ معه هنا.
So I pretended to be lame
لذلك تظاهرت بأنني أعرج
to make him think that he's over me.
ليجعله يعتقد أنه تجاوزني.
What a good story.
يا لها من قصة جيدة.
Why don't you be a screenwriter?
لماذا لا تكون كاتب سيناريو؟
So you think
هكذا تعتقد
what I was doing
ما كنت أفعله
and sacrificing for my family
والتضحية من أجل عائلتي
is just a story?
هي مجرد قصة؟
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I didn't know you were doing it for your family.
لم أكن أعلم أنك كنت تفعل ذلك من أجل عائلتك.
I shouldn't have said that.
لا ينبغي أن أقول ذلك.
But you pretended to be lame
لكنك تظاهرت بأنك أعرج
and fooled me indeed.
وخدعتني حقًا.
I can keep your secret if you want me to.
يمكنني الاحتفاظ بسرك إذا كنت تريد مني ذلك.
Promise me one condition.
اعدني بشرط واحد
Alright, just say it.
حسنًا ، قلها فقط.
Give me free access
أعطني حرية الوصول
to your office.
إلى مكتبك.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
The MOHS Group
مجموعة MOHS
is so big.
هو كبير جدا.
Why I don't see anyone?
لماذا لا أرى أحدا؟
Stop.
قف.
How do you usually go up there?
كيف تصعد هناك عادة؟
Usually,
عادة،
Xu Weilai carries me up.
Xu Weilai يحملني.
He's off today.
هو خارج اليوم.
Alright,
على ما يرام،
I'll carry you up.
سأحملك.
Come on.
هيا.
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
Yes.
نعم.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Come on.
هيا.
Oh,
أوه،
forget it.
انسى ذلك.
What?
ماذا؟
No one is around here today.
لا أحد موجود هنا اليوم.
I'll do it by myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
I'll walk up on my own.
سأمشي لوحدي.
OK.
نعم.
Chen.
تشين.
Chen,
تشين ،
what are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Mu Liu,
مو ليو ،
do you need my help?
هل تحتاج مساعدتي
- No. - Yes.
- لا نعم.
Chen,
تشين ،
don't you know
لا تعرف
how to be nice to your woman?
كيف تكون لطيفا مع امرأتك؟
Liu,
ليو ،
let me help you.
دعني اساعدك.
OK, thank you.
حسنا شكرا لك.
Chen,
تشين ،
I've taken the wheelchair up.
لقد أخذت الكرسي المتحرك.
Come on up, you two.
تعال ، أنتما الاثنان.
Oh, my!
أوه يا!
Chen,
تشين ،
are your legs
ساقاك
really...
حقًا...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
He doesn't like people touching him.
لا يحب أن يلمسه الناس.
I was just
كنت فقط
caring about him.
يهتم به.
When did they
عندما فعلوا
get so close?
اقترب جدا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Eh?
ايه؟
Well,
نحن سوف،
I...
أنا...
I think your office is in a mess,
أعتقد أن مكتبك في حالة من الفوضى ،
so I'm tidying it up for you.
لذلك أنا أرتب الأمر لك.
My office is in a mess?
مكتبي في حالة من الفوضى؟
Eh.
إيه.
How about your desk?
ماذا عن مكتبك؟
Does it need cleaning?
هل تحتاج للتنظيف؟
No.
رقم.
Just have a rest.
فقط خذ قسطا من الراحة.
The cabinet?
مجلس الوزراء؟
Let me help you clean up the cabinet.
دعني أساعدك في تنظيف الخزانة.
Just leave it.
فقط دعها.
Mo Feng?
مو فنغ؟
("Pollen Shop of Dream")
("متجر حبوب اللقاح للأحلام")
"Pollen Shop of Dream"?
"متجر حبوب اللقاح للأحلام"؟
Boss.
رئيس.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Sorry to interrupt.
معذرة للمقاطعة.
Well,
نحن سوف،
I'll go back now.
سأعود الآن.
("Pollen Shop of Dream")
("متجر حبوب اللقاح للأحلام")
(Share Purchase Agreement)
(اتفاقية شراء حصة)
Mr. Mu,
السيد.  نحن،
are you sure you want to give me the Mu's shares?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد أن تعطيني أسهم Mu؟
People in the Mu Group are of different minds
الناس في مجموعة Mu لديهم عقول مختلفة
in addition to a financial crisis.
بالإضافة إلى الأزمة المالية.
Your cooperation with me
تعاونك معي
is a great help to the Mu.
هو مساعدة كبيرة لمو.
Why do you want me to get engaged to Mu Liu?
لماذا تريدني أن أخطب مو ليو؟
Only if she marries into your Mo family
فقط إذا تزوجت من عائلة مو الخاصة بك
can the Mu Group maintain its reputation.
يمكن أن تحافظ مجموعة Mu على سمعتها.
If Liu wants to break off the engagement,
إذا أراد ليو قطع الخطوبة ،
our cooperation can continue.
يمكن أن يستمر تعاوننا.
My lawyer Mr. Luo will supervise the whole cooperation process.
سيشرف محامي السيد لوه على عملية التعاون بأكملها.
If you break the agreement,
إذا خرقت الاتفاقية ،
Mr. Luo will cancel the cooperation.
السيد لو سوف يلغي التعاون.
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
that Mo Chen is an otaku.
أن مو تشن هو أوتاكو.
Eh?
ايه؟
Isn't Xu Weilai off today?
أليس Xu Weilai متوقفًا اليوم؟
If you dare
اذا كنت تجرؤ
to put these...
لوضع هذه ...
Romance comics.
كاريكاتير الرومانسية.
If you put these things
إذا وضعت هذه الأشياء
in my drawer again,
في درجي مرة أخرى ،
just get out of the company.
فقط اخرج من الشركة.
I did it because I wanted you to learn
لقد فعلت ذلك لأنني أردت أن تتعلم
how to develop a relationship.
كيفية تطوير العلاقة.
I don't need that.
لا أحتاج ذلك.
You must need this.
يجب أن تحتاج هذا.
Look,
نظرة،
this is all the information
هذه هي كل المعلومات
about those between us and the acquisition of the Mu.
حول تلك التي بيننا وبين الاستحواذ على Mu.
It's all here.
كل شيء هنا.
But we don't know
لكننا لا نعرف
(Starwu acquired 26% of the Mu Group) how they managed
(استحوذت Starwu على 26٪ من مجموعة Mu Group) كيف تداروا
to get Mu Bingyun's shares.
للحصول على أسهم Mu Bingyun.
Looks like they have made a move
يبدو أنهم اتخذوا خطوة
on the Mu Group ahead of us.
على مجموعة Mu التي تنتظرنا.
(They also participated in)
(شاركوا أيضًا في)
(Mr. Mu's overseas trip.)
(رحلة السيد مو الخارجية.)
So you mean
لذلك تقصد
that they have something to do with the Mus' accident?
أن لهم علاقة بحادث المصحف؟
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪